[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Denzel Washington is named after his father who was in turn named after the doctor who had delivered him.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these singers had a daughter named Natalie?", "correct_answer": "Nat King Cole", "incorrect_answers": ["Yoko Lennon", "Dean Martin", "Frank Sinatra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1980 film by French director Alan Resnais features Gerard Depardieu in a starring role.  The translation of the title in English is loosely:  My Uncle is....", "correct_answer": "... An American.", "incorrect_answers": ["... My Uncle.", "... Most Avuncular.", "... Living Upstairs from Me."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jewish American actress Fran Drescher, famous for her nasal New York accent, played in the movie Saturday Night Fever.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These two physicists received the 1951 Nobel Prize for Physics for their pioneering work popularly known as splitting the atom.", "correct_answer": "John Cockroft and Ernest Walton", "incorrect_answers": ["Eugene Wigner and Lyman Briggs", "Lise Meitner and Otto Robert Frisch", "Leo Szilard and Edward Teller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries is believed to possess the largest apple cultivars collection in the world?", "correct_answer": "England", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "China", "United States"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many subspecies of Red Fox are found in India?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "None. Red Fox are not native to India.", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Indonesian name of the Mount Merapi volcano, Gunung Merapi, mean in English?", "correct_answer": "Mountain of Fire", "incorrect_answers": ["Gods Wrath", "Cursed Mountain", "Hell Mountain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1992 movie, My Cousin Vinnie, Ralph Macchio asks his cousin Vinnie to be his lawyer. What was  Vinnies last name?", "correct_answer": "Gambini", "incorrect_answers": ["Giradelli", "Gianfredo", "Barcolli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Sonny want to rob the bank in the film Dog Day Afternoon?", "correct_answer": "To pay for his boyfriends sex change operation", "incorrect_answers": ["To pay the rent.", "To start a new life in a new country", "To pay for a new car"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1386, a cow in France was executed by public hanging for the murder of a child.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Champagne, featured in at least eight Bond movies, does fictional spy James Bond prefer?", "correct_answer": "Bollinger", "incorrect_answers": ["Ruinart", "Dom P\u00e9rignon", "Moet et Chandon"]}]